Clarence Jarvis Photograph Collection, 1952-1960
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Clarence Jarvis Photograph Collection, 1952-1960
MS 349
Jarvis, Clarence
The photographs in this collection are of various locations in coastal Mexico, particularly Baja California, Alamos, Mazatlan, and Tepic. The photographs document seaside resorts, landscapes, cityscapes, and the local people in these areas during the 1950s.
.75 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Not much is known about the photographer, Clarence Jarvis, but it is presumed he was from the Tucson area. However, Mr. Jarvis had an excellent eye for framing a shot, as is evident in many of the photographs depicting fishermen and their boats, streetscapes, and children.
Organization
This collection is organized into 1 series
Series 1: Clarence Jarvis Photograph Collection, 1952-1960
Scope and Content Note
Consists of one box of black and white photographs of Clarence Jarvis' trips to Mexico during 1952-1960.
Access Terms
Jarvis, Clarence -- Photographer
Mexico -- Pictorial works
Baja California (Mexico: Peninsula) -- Pictorial works
Alamos (Sonora, Mexico) -- Pictorial works
Mazatlán (Sinaloa, Mexico) -- Pictorial works
Tepic (Mexico) -- Pictorial works
Container List
- Series 1: Clarence Jarvis Photograph Collection, 1952-1960
  - Acaponeta / Mazatlan / Tepic areas. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alamos, Sonora. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Adras Island (Baja California). 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ensenada (Baja California). 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Guaymas (Sonora). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hermosillo (Sonora). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Mazatlan (Sinaloa). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - San Felipe (Baja California). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - San Felipe (Baja California). 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - San Felipe (Baja California). 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - San Blas (Nayarit). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Santa Tamas (Baja California). 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Santa Tamas (Baja California). 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Tepic (Nayarit). 1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tepic / Penitas area. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Unidentified. no date (Box 1, Folder 25)